<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AnimalClaasification</string>
    <string name="sample_baike_info">The dog (Canis lupus familiaris) is a carnivorous mammal of the family Canidae and the genus Canis.
        It is known as one of the "six domestic animals" along with the horse, ox, sheep, pig, and chicken.
        The size and coat color of dogs vary by breed, but they generally have a well-proportioned body, a relatively long muzzle, oval-shaped eyes, and ears that can be either erect or drooping.
        They have strong limbs, with five toes on the front paws and four on the hind paws, equipped with non-retractable claws.
        Their tails can be curled or sickle-shaped.Dogs are found all over the world. They are primarily meat-eaters but also consume dog food, human leftovers, fruits, and snacks.
        Dogs do not sweat; instead, they regulate their body temperature by panting with their mouths open and tongues out.
        They are seasonal monoestrous animals, typically entering heat in the spring (March-May) and autumn (September-November).
        The gestation period for a dog is usually around three months, and they can sometimes give birth to ten to twelve puppies at once.
        Smaller breeds may have smaller litters of four or five, with one or two puppies being more common. The lifespan of a dog is relatively short, averaging around 12 years.
        Scientists believe that dogs were domesticated from gray wolves by early humans between 15,000 and 40,000 years ago.
        Today, as the most popular pet, they are known as "man's best friend." Dogs are intelligent, brave, loyal, and empathetic, making them useful for a wide range of purposes.
        For this reason, dogs are loved and protected in almost every country. Through long-term breeding, humans have developed their specific talents and traits for various purposes, making dogs one of the most diverse domestic animals.
        They have been bred for meat, hunting, guarding, reconnaissance, herding, performance, racing, guidance, sled-pulling, experiments, and companionship.</string>
</resources>